<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>c13n</title>
    <link>https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on c13n</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/content/posts/c13n.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/content/posts/c13n.html</guid>
      <description>What is c13n Sitting on top of Bitcoin &amp;amp; LightningNetwork layer, c13n is a component that makes your interaction with LN much easier. It acts as an intermediate layer between your application and your LN Node, without introducing any centralization characteristics.
c13n utilizes the node&amp;rsquo;s interface to achieve a higher-level API, easy for devs to get used to and to start building on top of right away.
One of the main priorities of c13n is to be based as much as possible on Lightning Network communication (through micro-payments), and to utilize clearnet the least possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Goal and Vision</title>
      <link>https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/content/posts/vision.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://c13n-io.github.io/c13n.io/content/posts/vision.html</guid>
      <description>Our goal is to create a common baseline for Lightning Applications. We want applications to have compatibility on the network layer as well as the application layer (for more info check c13n-payload-protocol).
Making different chatting applications able to normally communicate with each other is a great milestone for this ecosystem.
We envision an augmented ecosystem of services &amp;amp; apps over the Lightning Network, with easy integration and no compatibility friction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
